<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home Page on HAT RUN 50K</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/</link><description>Recent content in Home Page on HAT RUN 50K</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/resume/</guid><description>Web developer Skills Javascript React Next.js Git HTML CSS WordPress Experience Co-founder/Lead Developer - explorevanx.com San Diego, CA 8/2018 – Present
Develop, deploy &amp;amp; maintain business website using Next.js Audacious Inquiry Software Engineer I Baltimore, MD 3/2014 – 2/2018
Develop, deploy &amp;amp; maintain company website in Wordpress Hold weekly status calls with Government Leadership Helped grow JIRA usage from 10 projects to 45+ projects Support clients on daily usage of JIRA/Confluence software, focusing on application-related subjects via direct contact as well as helpdesk tickets Software Engineer II Baltimore, MD 2/2018 – 6/2019</description></item><item><title>Race Rules</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/race-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/race-rules/</guid><description>Absolutely NO Transferring of bib numbers. Registered runners only! This is critical to the safe tracking of all participants and the future of this event. If you are caught transferring or selling your bib, using a pacer or running as a bandit, you will be barred from future events.
Time Constraints will be STRICTLY enforced. These are not suggestions and are no longer up to the discretion of event staff or participants.</description></item><item><title>Runners</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/runners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/runners/</guid><description>The Course The course is mostly single track trail with a mix of open fields, dirt road and some paved road. The course features nearly 4,300 feet of climbing. There is a starting loop of 3.6 miles followed by two identical loops of 13.7 miles. There are 4 stream crossings that can be challenging depending on the water level – there is always the chance of getting wet feet.
HAT 50K on www.</description></item><item><title>Spectators</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/spectators/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/spectators/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Volunteer</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/volunteers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/hatrun/volunteers/</guid><description>Calling all VOLUNTEERS… The volunteers make this race what it is! Please come and join us again, if you don’t have the time of your life, we’ll refund you in full.
We’re using Ultrasignup again this year. Link will be available mid to late Febuary
Thank you again.
Ginn, Jeff, and Tim</description></item></channel></rss>